Guide to the Edwin H. Armstrong papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Alphabetical Files, 1886-1980
  - Emerson Litigation
    - Armstrong v. Emerson
      - Reference Numbers
        - 670--Emerson Advertisements, 1948-1950 (Box 70, Folder 7)
        - 681-682--Letter and Registered Receipts, 1948-1949 (Box 70, Folder 8)
        - 683--Depositions of Herzog, Abrams and Israel--Includes Notes by Unknown Author, 1952 (Box 70, Folder 9)
        - 684--Depositions of Abrams and Israel--RCA, "Overall Fidelity of Standard Broadcast and FM Receivers Manufactured in 1948," 1948, 1952, (3 Folders) (Box 70, Folder 10-12)
        - 685-686--Copy of K-3 Agreement Between Armstrong and Westinghouse--Copies of Assignment '447 Patent, 1923, 1927 (Box 70, Folder 13)
        - 687--Stipulation, Emerson Licenses from RCA, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 14)
        - De Mars, Paul
          - 690--Article, 1940 (Box 70, Folder 15)
          - 691-692--Deposition and Exhibits, 1940-1952 (Box 70, Folder 16)
          - 693-694--1940 1943, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 70, Folder 17-18)
        - 730--Bowles, Edward L--Biographical Sketch, Citations, Air Force Directive, 1943-1957 (Box 70, Folder 19)
        - 733-738--Articles, Publications, 1946-1957 (Box 71, Folder 1)
        - 739-745--War Department and Army and Air Force Technical Manuals, 1943-1954, (3 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 2-4)
        - 746-755--Publications--UNESCO, Commerce Department, Advertising Research Foundation, 1953-1957, undated, (3 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 5-7)
      - Index--Prior Art Cited by Defendant Against Armstrong Reissue Patent 21,660 and Patent '066, 1957, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 8-9)
      - Memoranda on References, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Notebooks--Harry Sadenwater
        - No. 1-- June 22, 1934 to July 30, 1940--1 through 259Y--Includes Original, (3 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 11-13)
        - No. 1-- June 22, 1934 to May 25, 1939--1 through 41--Original (Box 71, Folder 14)
        - No. 2-- January 9, 1939 to January 10, 1940--42 through 131--Original (Box 71, Folder 15)
        - No. 2-- July 30, 1940 to July 15, 1943--260 through 533--Includes Original, (2 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 16-17)
        - No. 3-- July 30, 1940 to July 15, 1943--260 through 533--Original (Box 71, Folder 18)
        - No. 3-- August 13, 1943 to March 20, 1948--534 through 648--Includes Original, (3 Folders) (Box 72, Folder 1-3)
        - No. 4-- March 18, 1940 to April 12, 1940--194X through 227--Original (Box 72, Folder 4)
        - No. 5-- April 14, 1940 to October 20, 1940--228 through 301--Original (Box 72, Folder 5)
        - No. 6-- October 21, 1940 to March 29, 1941--302 through 397--Original (Box 72, Folder 6)
        - No. 7-- March 31, 1941 to May 4, 1942--398 through 505--Original (Box 72, Folder 7)
        - No. 8-- May 4, 1942 to November 23, 1943--506 through 591--Original (Box 72, Folder 8)
        - No. 9-- December 7, 1943 to October 1944--592 through 612X--Original (Box 72, Folder 9)
        - No. 10-- October 6, 1944 to March 12, 1945--613 through 616YB--Original (Box 72, Folder 10)
        - No. 11-- March 21, 1945 to September 9, 1945--616YC through 616YP--Original (Box 72, Folder 11)
        - No. 12-- September 21, 1945 to April 23, 1947--616YQ through 622X--Original (Box 72, Folder 12)
        - No.13-- May 15, 1947 to March 20, 1948--622Y through 648--Original (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - Patents
        - German Wide Swing Application
          - Brief in Draft Form, Various Suggestions, Brief As Filed, 1952-1953 (Box 73, Folder 1)
          - References, 1953, undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
          - Papers in Dutch Application, 1934-1938 (Box 73, Folder 3)
          - Reply to Briefs Filed by Blaupunket-Werke, 1952-1953 (Box 73, Folder 4)
          - Drafts, 1953 (Box 73, Folder 5)
          - Intermediate Decision of Appeal Board, 1954 (German) (Box 73, Folder 6)
          - Briefs, Reply's, Decision, 1952-1954 (German) (Box 73, Folder 7)
        - Analysis of Features Cited By Emerson Against Armstrong Patent, undated (Box 73, Folder 8)
        - Prior Art Cited By Defendant Against Armstrong Reissue Patent 21,660, undated (Box 73, Folder 9)
        - Prior Art Cited by Defendant Against Armstrong Patent '069, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 73, Folder 10-11)
        - File Wrappers
          - US Patent 1,941,069, December 26, 1933--Serial No. 653,237, Filed January 24, 1933--Includes Original Notes and Figures, 1932-1933, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 12)
          - US Patent 2,215, 284, September 17, 1940--Serial No. 319,569, Filed February 19, 1940--Reissue Patent 21,660, December 17, 1940--Includes Correspondence, 1940-1947 (Box 73, Folder 13)
          - US Patent 21,660, December 17, 1940--Serial No. 362,177, Filed October 21, 1940--Filed in Canada, February 1, 1940 Serial No. 479,948, 1940-1949 (Box 73, Folder 14)
        - Emerson Correspondence, 1940-1952, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 15)
        - Prior Art Cited by Defendant Against Armstrong Patent '069, undated (Box 73, Folder 16)
        - Heising's Notes on Prior Art Patents Cited by Examiner, 1957-1958 (Box 73, Folder 17)
        - Exhibits for Dana Raymond, 1958 October 14 (Box 73, Folder 18)
        - Report of Harry W. Houck, 1958 (Box 73, Folder 19)
        - Correspondence and Notes of Raymond A. Heising, 1957-1958, (2 Folders) (Box 73, Folder 20-21)
        - Prior Art Cited by Defendant Against Armstrong Reissue Patent 21,660, undated (Box 73, Folder 22)
        - "Explanation of Wide Band Patent"--Typed copy, undated (Box 73, Folder 23)
        - Decision of German Patent Office of November 15, 1954--Includes Translation, 1952-1954 (German) (Box 73, Folder 24)
        - Legal Documents, undated (Box 73, Folder 25)
        - Transparencies--Claims v. Patents, undated (Box 73, Folder 26)
      - Emerson Service Manuals
        - 1951-1952 (Box 73, Folder 27)
        - 1950-1951, (3 Folders) (Box 74, Folder 1-3)
      - Transcripts--Stenographers Minutes
        - 1958 October 10, 14-17, 20-24, 27-31, November 3, (10 Folders) (Box 74, Folder 4-13)
      - Transcripts--Stenographers Minutes
        - 1958 November 5-6, 10-12, 18, 1959 May 6, (3 Folders) (Box 75, Folder 1-3)
      - Abstracts--Part I-III, 1958, (3 volumes) (Box 75)
  - Engstrom, E.W.--Correspondence and Testimony, 1933-1951 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Espenschied, Lloyd--Correspondence, 1933-1951, (2 Folders) (Box 75, Folder 5-6)
  - Everitt, W.L.--"Frequency Modulation," 1940 November (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Facsimile System--Correspondence and Articles, 1940-1951 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - FADA Radio and Electric Company Litigation
    - FADA--Marion Armstrong v. FADA Radio and Electric Company--Pleadings and Answers to Allegations, 1956 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Fake FM Sets--Advertisements, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Fancher, H.B.--"Microwave Television Relay Networks" undated (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Farren, L.I.--"Phase Detectors-Some Theoretical and Practical Aspects," 1946 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Fassbender, H. and Kurlbaum--"Dependence of the Range of Very Short Waves on the Height of the Transmitter Above the Ground," undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Faught Company--General, 1946-1953, (2 Folders) (Box 76, Folder 5-6)
  - Fine, H.--UHF "Propagation within Line of Sight," 1951 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Fink, D.G.
    - "From the Mountaintops," 1939 April (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - "The Transistor-A Crystal Triode," 1949 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Fleming, J.A.--"Approximate Theory of the Flat Projector (Franklin) Aerial Used in the Marconi Beam System of Wireless Technology," 1927 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Fletcher, H. and Galt, R.H.--"The Perception of Speech and its Relation to Telephony," 1950 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Flowers, J.W.--"The Direct Measurement of Lightning Current," 1941 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Fly, James L.--General, 1934-1944 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Electronics: Radio, Communication, Industrial Applications of Electron Tubes…Engineering and Manufacture, 1939 October (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Tele-Tech and Electronic Industries, volume 12, number 4, 1953 April (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - The Franklin Institute--Correspondence and Awards (Photograph), 1940-1951 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Freeland, E.C.--"FM Receiver Design Problems," 1949 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Fortune Magazine
    - Correspondence, Articles and volume 38, number 2, 1939-1951, (3 Folders) (Folder 18-20)
    - Volume 37, Number 2, 1948 February (Box 262, Folder 9)
  - Finance
    - Experimental Expenses Regarding FM, 1933-1949 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - General, 1945-1947 (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence and Bills, 1947-1954, (3 Folders) (Box 76, Folder 23-25)
  - Frequency Modulation (FM)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1928-1944, (2 Folders) (Box 76, Folder 26-27)
    - Insignia, undated (Box 76, Folder 28)
    - Census Map, 1950 (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - Receiver Development--Proceedings of the IRE, 1944 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Progress--Proceedings of the IRE, 1945-1946 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Bibliography, Articles and Publications, 1922-1947 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Publications, 1941-1950 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence--Armstrong to Pupin--Report Regarding 19 Years of Experiments in Lab, 1933 April 3 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Draft of Paper on FM and Its Future Uses, undated (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - "A Method of Reducing Disturbances In Radio Signaling by a System of Frequency Modulation"--Typewritten Copy with Corrections, undated (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1935-1951 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - General, 1939-1944 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Hostile Propaganda, 1941-1949, (2 Folders) (Box 77, Folder 10-11)
    - Readings From Test, 1953 March 19-20 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - FM Association (FMA)--Promotional Booklet, undated (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - FMA Meeting Memoranda and Correspondence, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - "FM Broadcasting"--Booklet by RCA, undated (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Clinic Papers, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Bibliography, 1945-1946 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - FM Broadcasters, Inc.--Dick Dorrance--Correspondence, 1940-1945 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - FMA Meeting, 1947-1948, (2 Folders) (Box 77, Folder 19-20)
    - FMA Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - Transmitter Advanced Development Section, 1935 (Box 77, Folder 22)
    - FM Survey Pulse Reports, 1950-1953, (3 Folders) (Box 77, Folder 23-25)
    - Testing
      - Hourly Median Analysis Worksheets, Westhampton, 1947 (Box 77, Folder 26)
      - Calibration Curves--Receiver and Antenna Input, circa 1948 (Box 77, Folder 27)
      - Analysis of Recordings on 44.1 and 92.1 Megacycles at Mt. Holly, New Jersey, 1947 November (Box 77, Folder 28)
      - Worksheets and Curves for Daily Analysis of Recordings of 92.1 and 44.1 at New London, CT, 1947 October-November (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Original Curves, Daily Analysis of Westhampton Recordings, 1947 September-October (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Photostats of Daily Analysis of Westhampton Beach Recordings of W2XMN and W2XEA, 1947 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Hourly Analysis of Recordings Made at Westhampton Beach, 1947 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Composite Analysis--Worksheets, Original Curves, Negatives, New London, CT, 1947 October 23-December 8 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Composite Curve from Daily Curve Analysis of Westhampton Beach Recordings and Curves Showing Ratio, 1947 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - Composite Curves and Analysis, 1949 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - Reception Reports Including Reception through Thunderstorm--Includes Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Comparison of Analysis Covering 2 Day Period and 31 Day Period at Westhampton, 1947 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - Field Intensities Beyond Line of Sight at 45.5 and 91 mcs, 1945 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Copy of Mt. Holly Log Book, 1949 January (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Logbooks
        - 44.1 Mc and 93.1 Mc Field Strength Calibrations--Mt. Holly, New Jersey,1949 February (Box 80, Folder 3)
        - W2XMN--F.G. Hargesheimer--Alpine, NJ, 1946-1948 (Box 80, Folder 4)
        - Unidentified, 1946-1949, (2 Folders) (Box 80, Folder 5-6)
        - Southampton and Montgomery, 1950-1951 (Box 80, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 80, Folder 8)
        - Data Sheets and Calibration Curves for Receivers Used at Mt. Holly and Record of W2XMN and W2XEA Transmitter Power, 1949 (Box 80, Folder 9)
        - Worksheets for Analysis of Recordings Made at Mt. Holly, 1949 February-March (Box 80, Folder 10)
        - Worksheets for Westhampton Beach Recordings Analyzed at Jansky and Bailey, undated (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Godley, Paul--Correspondence, 1936-1950 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Gernsback, H.--"Can We Radio the Planets?," 1927 February (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Friede, Herbert A.--FCC Testimony, 1947 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Friis, H.T.--"Noise Figures of Radio Receivers," Proceedings of the IRE, 1944 July (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Friis, R.W. and K.D. Smith--"An Unattended Broadcast Microwave Repeater For the TD-2 Radio Relay System," 1951 November (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Flyer, G.W. and J.A. Worcester--"A New Armstrong Frequency Modulated Receiver," 1939 July (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - "A Noise Free Radio Receiver," 1939 July (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Gavin, M.R.--"Frequency Modulator of An Oscillator," 1948 September (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - German Broadcasting--Bayerland, 1952 November (German) (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - General Electric
    - Correspondence--Includes Blueprints and Photographs, 1930-1953, (4 Folders) (Box 81, Folder 1-4)
    - Frequency Modulation Demonstration, 1939 April 5-7 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Instruction Booklets--Includes Letter fromWeir, 1953 December, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 81, Folder 6-7)
    - Report No. 19413--Investigation of Adjacent Channel Interference, 1931 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - GE Contract and Correspondence, 1944-1946 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence with C.A. Priest, 1952 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Letter From Joseph Behr, 1953--Typed Telephone Conversation with Frank A. Gunther, 1953 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Blueprints, 1951-1953 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - "How W47A Did It; An FM Success Story," 1941 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - General Electric Review, "First Frequency Modulation Radio Receivers For High Fidelity Reception," 1939 September (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Frequency Modulation Receiver, CAT. 5100997--Piece of Actual Receiver Box Listing Parts, undated (Three Dimensional) (Box 259, Folder 2)
  - General Radio Company--Correspondence, 1950 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Germanium Diodes--Applications, Page 5, 1950 March 1 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Gerth, and W. Scheppmann--"Investigations into the Propagation Phenomena of Ultra-Short Waves," undated (German) (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Gilfillan Bros.--Correspondence, Papers, Blueprints, 1950 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Gilfillan Bros. Litigation
    - Armstrong v. Gilfillan Bros.
      - Legal Correspondence and Memoranda, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 25)
      - Reporters Transcript of Proceedings, 1955 October 17 (Box 80, Folder 26)
      - Chart, undated (Box 80, Folder 27)
      - Legal Documents, 1955, (2 Folders) (Box 80, Folder 28-29)
  - Gillingham, George O.--Correspondence, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - Gilman, G.W.--"Systems Engineering in Bell Telephone Laboratories," 1953 January (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Gleissberg, W--"Predictions for the Coming Sunspot Cycle," 1943 (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Goldberg, H. and E.L. Crosby--"Series Made Crystal Circuits," 1948 March (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - Goldmark, Peter C.--FCC Proceedings, 1944 (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - Gouriet, G.G.--"High Stability Oscillator," 1950 April (Box 80, Folder 35)
  - Grammer, G.--"Wide Band Frequency Modulation in Amateur Communications," 1940 January (Box 80, Folder 36)
  - Granlund, J.--"Interference in Frequency Modulation Reception," 1949 January (Box 80, Folder 37)
  - Experiments and Results in Wireless Telephone, 1907 January (Box 80, Folder 38)
  - Graphs and Charts
    - Hand drawn Graphs with Notes and Figures, 1946, undated (Box 80, Folder 39)
    - Unidentified Plotted Graphs, 1933--Paper, "Schenectady Transmitters," undated--"Comparison of Service Areas for Amplitude and Frequency Modulated Signals"--Chart by Hans Roder, 1937 December (Box 80, Folder 40)
    - Curves--Empire State to Haddonfield, NJ, 1933-1935 (Box 80, Folder 41)
    - Profile Graph--Alpine, NJ to Westhampton Beach, Long Island, undated (Box 80, Folder 42)
    - Profile Graph--WGYN--New York City to Westhampton Beach, Long Island, undated (Box 80, Folder 43)
    - Data and Charts of Cathode Bias, 1946, undated (Box 247, Folder 1)
    - Map of Massachusetts--Rural vs. Urban Coverage--Microvolt per Meter Contour, undated (Photostat) (Box 263)
    - Plots of Received Signal Strengths from Various FM Radio Stations at Multiple Transmission Frequencies, 1945 (Photostats) (Box 263)
    - Profile Map--Projected from W2AG, Yonkers to Westhampton Beach, undated (Box 263)
    - Plots of Received Signal Strengths from Various Radio Stations at Multiple Transmission Frequencies, 1945 (Photostats) (Box 264)
  - Gresky, G.--"How Reflectors Work with Short Electric Waves," 1928 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Greiser, T.J. and Paterson, A.C.--"A Broadband Transcontinental Radio Relay System," 1951 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Grimes, David--"The Manufacturers Say," 1941 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Gross Distributors, Inc.--Correspondence, 1940-1950 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Grosskopf, J.--"Antennas with Feedback," 1949 (German) (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Guillemin, E.A.--"Criticism of Crosby Article on Frequency Modulation Noise Characteristics," undated (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Guther, B.--"Westinghouse, Type B 940-960 Megacycle Communication Equipment," undated (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Guy, R.and R.M. Morris--"NBC Frequency Modulation Field Test," undated (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - Guy, R.F.--"The Why and How of Frequency Modulation," 1940 (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - FM and UHF, 1943-1944 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Hahnemann, W.--"On the Recent Development of the Machine Transmitter for Short Wavelengths," 1928 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Hahnemann, W. and Gerth--"Common Frequency Broadcasting," 1929 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - Halstead, W.S.--"Multiple Program Transmission," undated (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - Hanson, O.B.--"Historic Highlights in Developing the Radio Broadcasting and Television Arts," 1952 (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - Hasse, A.P.--"New One-Tube Limiter-Discriminator for FM," 1950 (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - Hastings Instrument Co., Inc.--"Hastings-Raydist Indicator," 1949 (Box 81, Folder 30)
  - Hathaway, J.L.--"High Frequency Pre-Emphasis," 1939 (Box 81, Folder 31)
  - Hazeltine, A.--"Deflection Control Tubes," 1936 (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - Heinl, Robert O.--Correspondence and Heinl News Service, 1948-1950 (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - Hennock, Frieda B.--Correspondence, 1948 (Box 81, Folder 34)
  - "Armstrong Stirs Radio Club with 35 Year Old FM Hoax Story," 1948 (Box 81, Folder 35)
  - Hillard, V.--Radio Telephones Guide the "Blitz Buggies," 1944 (Box 81, Folder 36)
  - Hickman, C.N.--"Sound Recording on Magnetic Tape," 1937 (Box 81, Folder 37)
  - High Fidelity--Clippings, 1953-1954, (2 Folders) (Box 81, Folder 38-39)
  - Hill, D.R.--"New Castle Design Improves Tube Reliability," 1951 (Box 81, Folder 40)
  - Hogan, John--Correspondence, Articles, Blueprints, 1939-1949 (Box 81, Folder 41)
  - Hirschmann, Ira--Correspondence, 1949-1953 (Box 81, Folder 42)
  - Hoover, Herbert--"Engineers"--Speech, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 43)
  - Holcomb, P.--"Basic Principles of the Varioplex Telegraph," 1940 (Box 81, Folder 44)
  - Hoffman Radio Corporation Litigation
    - Armstrong v. Hoffman Radio Corporation
      - Affidavits, 1954 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Legal Documents, 1956 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Agreement and General Release and Covenant Not to Sue, 1956-1957 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Charts, undated (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Horne, Josh (WFMA)--Correspondence, 1949-1951, (2 Folders) (Box 82, Folder 6-7)
  - Huber, G.H.--"A15-KC Carrier Program Channel," 1949 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Hughes, J.W.--"Stabilizing Direct-Voltage Supplies," 1947 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Hund, August--Correspondence and Clippings, 1941-1945 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - The Institution of Radio Engineers (IRE)
    - Correspondence, 1936-1952, (4 Folders) (Box 82, Folder 11-14)
    - Australia--Correspondence and Articles, 1950-1954 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Insurance Matters--General, 1947-1952 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - International Business Machines (IBM)--General, 1939-1954 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Interdepartment Radio Advisory Committee (IRAC)--General, 1944-1945 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - International Telecommunications Conference, Atlantic City, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - International Telephone and Telegraph Corporation--General and Litigation, 1938-1953 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Jansky and Bailey--Statements and Reports, 1944-1953, (2 Folders) (Box 82, Folder 21-22)
  - Jaffe, David L.--Articles, 1938-1940 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Jefferson, H.--"Filter Design Tables Based on Preferred Numbers (High Pass Filters)," 1946 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Jett, E.K.
    - General, 1946-1951 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - "Radio Interference Problems from Operation of Electro-Medical Apparatus," 1941 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Statement Before Committee on Appropriations, House of Representatives, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Johnson, Edwin--General, 1949-1950 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, J.B.--"Thermal Agitation of Electricity in Conductors," 1928 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, J.B. and F.B. Llewellyn--"Limits to Amplification," 1934 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Johnston, R.and A.G. Ratz--"A Graphical Method for Flip-Flop Design," 1953 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Jolliffe, C.B.--General, 1926-1947 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Jones, Robert F.--General, 1950 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Jones, Thomas M.--Armstrong Conquers Radio Static in Columbia's Research Laboratory," 1939 (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Journal of the Society of Motion Picture Engineers, Articles, 1938-1940 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Kalmus, H.P.--"Some Notes on Superregeneration with Particular Emphasis on its Possibilities for Frequency Modulation," 1944 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Keall, O.E.--"Interference in Relation to Amplitude, Phase and Frequency Modulated Systems," 1941 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Keen, A.W.--"Linear Saw Tooth Generators," 1948 (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - Kilgour, C.E. and Glessner, J.M.--"Diode Detection Analysis," 1933 (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - Kiplinger Magazine Articles and Correspondence, 1950 (Box 82, Folder 34)
  - Kirke, H.L.
    - "Frequency Modulation: BBC Field Trails," 1936 (Box 82, Folder 35)
    - "An Experimental Investigation of Car Ignition Interference," 1947 (Box 82, Folder 36)
  - Klappenbach, W.--Correspondence, 1941-1953 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Municipal Signal Engineer Articles, 1941 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Klipsch, Paul--Articles and Correspondence, 1941-1953 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Lafferty, J.M.--"Lanthanum Boride Cathodes," undated (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Landon, V.D.--Articles, 1936-1941 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Lang, F.--"The System with Frequency Multiplication in Iron Core Transformers," undated (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Laval University--Correspondence, 1948-1952 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Lawson, D.I.--"Frequency Modulation-Its Production by Phase Shifting the Side Bands of an Amplitude Modulated Wave," 1940 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Lee, Robert E.--Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Levy, M.--"Power Pulse Generator," 1946 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Lemke, William--Articles and Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Armstrong's Licensed FM Broadcasters--Lists, 1948, (2 Folders) (Box 83, Folder 18-19)
  - Laboratory--Notes--Includes Early Notes
    - Address Book, undated (Box 89, Folder 4)